Finding Aid for Bureau of School Services (University of Michigan) Records 1871-1992
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Accreditation Inspection Reports 1871-1992
  - C-D
    - Centreville
      - Centreville High School 1919-1992 (Box 26)
    - Champion
      - Champion High School 1921-1968 (Box 26)
    - Channing
      - Channing High School 1923-1963 (Box 26)
    - Charlevoix
      - Charlevoix High School 1902-1992 (Box 27)
    - Charlotte
      - Charlotte High School 1905-1992 (Box 27)
    - Chassell
      - Chassell Township High School 1948-1956 (Box 27)
      - J.A. Doelle High School 1940-1956 (Box 27)
    - Chatham
      - Rock River (Township Rural Agricultural) High School 1948-1956 (Box 27)
    - Cheboygan
      - Cheboygan Catholic High School 1952-1981 (Box 27)
      - Cheboygan (Area) High School 1905-1992 (Box 27)
    - Chelsea
      - Chelsea High School 1905-1992 (Box 27)
      - St. Mary's High School 1916 (Box 27)
    - Chesaning
      - Chesaning Union High School 1902-1992 (Box 28)
      - Maple Grove (St. Michael) High School (see Maple Grove) (Box 28)
      - Our Lady of Perpetual Help School 1938 (Box 28)
    - Clare
      - Clare High School 1905-1992 (Box 28)
    - Clarkston
      - Clarkston (Senior) High School 1921-1991 (Box 28)
    - Clarksville
      - Clarksville High School 1926-1945 (Box 28)
    - Clawson
      - Clawson High School 1926-1992 (Box 28)
      - Log Cabin High School 1926-1947 (Box 28)
    - Clayton
      - Clayton High School 1928-1943 (Box 28)
    - Climax
      - Climax-Scotts High School 1929-1992 (Box 29)
    - Clinton
      - Boysville High School 1954 (Box 29)
      - Clinton High School 1909-1992 (Box 29)
      - Thomas More High School 1967-1970 (Box 29)
    - Clio
      - Clio Area High School 1915-1992 (Box 29)
    - Coldwater
      - Coldwater High School 1903-1992 (Box 29)
      - St. Charles High School 1925-1967 (Box 29)
    - Coleman
      - Coleman High School 1911-1992 (Box 30)
    - Coloma
      - Coloma High School 1913-1991 (Box 30)
    - Colon
      - Colon High School 1912-1992 (Box 30)
    - Columbiaville (Marathon Township)
      - Columbiaville High School 1929-1953 (Box 30)
    - Comins Township (see Fairview) (Box 30)
    - Comstock
      - Comstock High School 1912-1992 (Box 30)
    - Comstock Park
      - Comstock Park High School 1927-1991 (Box 31)
    - Concord
      - Concord (Union) High School 1917-1991 (Box 31)
    - Constantine
      - Constantine High School 1905-1992 (Box 31)
    - Cooks
      - Inwood Consolidated (Big Bay de Noc) 1933-1992 (Box 31)
    - Coopersville
      - Coopersville High School 1911-1992 (Box 31)
    - Copemish
      - Copemish (Consolidated Rural Agricultural) High School 1929-1958 (Box 32)
    - Corunna
      - Corunna High School 1905-1992 (Box 32)
    - Covert
      - Covert High School 1924-1992 (Box 32)
    - Croswell
      - Croswell-Lexington High School 1909-1992 (Box 32)
    - Crystal
      - Crystal (Community) High School 1929-1956 (Box 32)
    - Crystal Falls
      - (Crystal Falls) Forest Park High School 1903-1992 (Box 32)
    - Custer
      - Custer High School (Mason County Eastern High School) 1927-1992 (Box 33)
    - Daggett
      - Daggett Township High School 1938-1942 (Box 33)
    - Dansville (Ingham Township)
      - Dansville Agricultural High School 1925-1992 (Box 33)
    - Davison
      - Davison High School 1914-1992 (Box 33)
    - Dearborn
      - Divine Child High School 1962-1992 (Box 33)
      - Edsel Ford High School 1956-1992 (Box 33)
      - Edison Institute 1935-1952 (Box 33)
      - Fordson High School 1927-1992 (Box 34)
      - Greenfield Village High School 1954 (Box 34)
      - Dearborn High School 1917-1992 (Box 34)
      - (Henry) Ford Trade School 1947-1952 (Box 34)
      - (Harvey H.) Lowry School 1948-1949 (Box 34)
        (see also Dearborn Heights: Annapolis High School)
      - Sacred Heart High School 1938-1975 (Box 34)
      - St. Alphonsus High School 1926-1992 (Box 34)
    - Dearborn Heights
      - Annapolis High School (formerly Harvey H. Lowry in Dearborn) 1948-1992 (Box 34)
      - Crestwood High School 1962-1992 (Box 35)
      - Riverside High School 1961-1984 (Box 35)
      - Robishaud High School 1961-1992 (Box 35)
      - Vista Maria High School 1974-1992 (Box 35)
    - Decatur
      - Decatur High School 1905-1992 (Box 35)
    - Deckerville
      - Deckerville (Community) High School 1916-1992 (Box 35)
    - Deerfield
      - Deerfield High School 1919-1991 (Box 36)
    - Delton
      - Delton (Kellogg) (Rural Agricultural) High School 1927-1992 (Box 36)
    - Detour
      - Detour (Area) High School 1921-1981 (Box 36)
    - Detroit 1966-1968 boxes 164-166]
      [see also Detroit High School Study Commission
      - All Saints High School 1923-1969 (Box 36)
      - Annunciation High School 1919-1966 (Box 36)
      - Archdiocese of Detroit School System 1981-1986 (Box 36)
      - Austin Catholic Preparatory School 1955-1978 (Box 36)
      - Benedictine High School 1958-1992 (Box 36)
      - Bishop Borgess High School 1971-1979 (Box 36)
      - Blessed Sacrament 1921-1957 (Box 37)
      - Cass Technical High School 1910-1992 (Box 37)
      - Cathedral Central High School 1919-1962 (Box 37)
      - Catholic Central High School 1929-1985 (Box 37)
      - Central High for Girls 1942-1974 (Box 37)
      - Central High School 1905-1992 (Box 38)
      - Central Evening High School 1924 (Box 38)
      - Cadshey High School 1934-1992 (Box 38)
      - Cody High School 1954-1992 (Box 38)
      - College High School 1924-1927 (Box 38)
      - Commerce High School (see Detroit High School of Commerce) (Box 38)
      - (Thomas M.) Cooley High School 1929-1985 (Box 38)
      - De La Salle Collegiate High School 1928-1983 (Box 39)
        (see also Warren)
      - Denby High School 1930-1986 (Box 39)
      - Detroit Collegiate Institute 1928-1929 (Box 39)
      - Detroit Conservatory of Music 1921-1922 (Box 39)
      - Detroit High School of Commerce 1925-1963 (Box 39)
      - Detroit Institute of Technology (Evening Program) 1924-1959 (Box 39)
      - Dominican High School 1940-1992 (Box 39)
      - East Catholic High School 1967-1992 (Box 40)
      - Eastern High School (see Martin Luther King High School) (Box 40)
      - (Jared W.) Finney (Junior/Senior) High School 1963-1986 (Box 40)
      - Henry Ford High School 1960-1986 (Box 40)
      - Free School 1974 (Box 40)
      - Guardian Angels High School 1938 (Box 40)
      - Hebrew Parochial School 1943-1946 (Box 40)
      - Higgins High School 1908-1914 (Box 40)
      - Hillel Day School of Metropolitan Detroit (Farmington) 1973 (Box 40)
      - Holy Name Institute 1925-1935 (Box 40)
      - Holy Redeemer High School 1924-1992 (Box 40)
      - Holy Redeemer Girls High School 1917-1943 (Box 40)
      - Holy Trinity High School 1922-1929 (Box 40)
      - Hudson High School 1916-1933 (Box 40)
      - Immaculata High School 1941-1983 (Box 41)
      - Jesuit (see University of Detroit Jesuit High School) (Box 41)
      - (Charles F.) Kettering High School 1968-1986 (Box 41)
      - Liggett School 1902-1964 (Box 41)
      - Lutheran High School West 1947-1992 (Box 41)
      - MacKenzie High School 1931-1992 (Box 41)
      - Martin Luther King High School (Eastern High School) 1902-1986 (Box 42)
      - McMillan High School 1909-1914 (Box 42)
      - (Sidney D.) Miller High School 1936-1957 (Box 42)
      - (Samuel C.) Mumford High School 1952-1986 (Box 42)
      - Murray-Wright (Cooperative/Vocational) High School 1948-1986 (Box 42)
      - Nativity of Our Lord High School 1950-1971 (Box 42)
      - Miss Newman's High School 1927-1952 (Box 42)
      - Northeastern High School 1919-1982 (Box 43)
      - Northern (Senior) High School 1924-1986 (Box 43)
      - Northern Evening High School 1920-1957 (Box 43)
      - Northwestern High School 1915-1986 (Box 43)
      - Osborn High School 1922-1986 (Box 43)
      - Our Lady of Mercy 1945-1964 (Box 43)
      - Patronage of St. Joseph 1952-1967 (Box 43)
      - (John J.) Pershing High School 1930-1986 (Box 44)
      - Redford High School 1925-1986 (Box 44)
      - Renaissance High School 1981-1986 (Box 44)
      - Rosary High School 1921-1973 (Box 44)
      - Sacred Heart High School 1945-1956 (Box 44)
      - Sacred Heart Seminary High School 1923-1970 (Box 44)
      - St. Agnes High School 1922-1966 (Box 44)
      - St. Ambrose High School 1924-1971 (Box 44)
      - St. Andrew High School 1943-1982 (Box 44)
      - Ste. Anne School 1927-1960 (Box 45)
      - St. Anthony High School 1928-1967 (merged with St. Elizabeth to form East Catholic High School) (Box 45)
      - St. Augustine High School 1956-1964 (Box 45)
      - St. Bernard High School 1925-1964 (Box 45)
      - St. Casimir High School 1935-1969 (Box 45)
      - St. Catherine High School 1925-1967 (Box 45)
      - St. Cecilia High School 1929-1967 (Box 45)
      - St. Charles High School 1926-1967 (Box 45)
      - St. Cyril High School 1952-1970 (Box 45)
      - St. David High School 1928-1971 (Box 45)
      - St. Elizabeth High School 1948-1969 (merged with St. Anthony to form East Catholic High School) (Box 45)
      - St. Francis de Sales High School 1938-1971 (Box 45)
      - St. Gabriel High School 1953-1970 (Box 46)
      - St. Gregory High School 1932-1969 (Box 46)
      - St. Hedwig High School 1941-1990 (Box 46)
      - St. Josophat High School 1927-1959 (Box 46)
      - St. Joseph High School 1921-1963 (Box 46)
      - St. Leo High School 1918-1970 (Box 46)
      - St. Martin High School 1938-1970 (Box 46)
      - St. Martin de Porres High School 1967-1991 (Box 46)
      - St. Mary of Redford High School 1928-1991 (Box 46)
      - St. Philip Neri High School 1939-1970 (Box 47)
      - St. Rita High School 1940-1972 (Box 47)
      - St. Rose (of Lima) High School 1928-1966 (Box 47)
      - St. Stanislaus High School 1931-1973 (Box 47)
      - St. Theresa High School 1923-1967 (Box 47)
      - St. Thomas High School 1940-1964 (Box 47)
      - St. Vincent de Paul High School 1917-1970 (Box 47)
      - Salesian (Catholic) High School 1950-1970 (Box 47)
      - Seminary of the Felician Sisters 1921-1965 (Box 47)
      - Servite High School 1953-1987 (Box 47)
      - Southeastern High School 1920-1986 (Box 47)
      - Southwestern High School 1918-1986 (Box 48)
      - Sweetest Heart of Mary High School 1941-1962 (Box 48)
      - University of Detroit Jesuit High School 1915-1992 (Box 48)
      - Visitation High School 1926-1967 (Box 48)
      - Vista Maria High School 1962-1975 (Box 48)
      - Western High School 1905-1986 (Box 48)
      - Woodmere High School 1906 (Box 48)
      - Yeshivath Beth Yehudah 1950 (Box 48)
      - YWCA School 1929-1930 (Box 48)
    - DeWitt (Box 49)
      - DeWitt High School 1938-1992 (Box 49)
    - Dexter
      - Dexter (Union) High School 1902-1992 (Box 49)
    - Dimondale
      - Dimondale High School 1929-1963 (Box 49)
    - Dollar Bay
      - Dollar Bay High School 1905-1992 (Box 49)
    - Dowagiac
      - Dowagiac Union High School circa 1893, 1906-1992 (Box 49)
    - Drayton Plains
      - Waterford-Kettering High School 1940-1992 (Box 49)
    - Dryden
      - Dryden Community High School 1915-1992 (Box 50)
    - Dundee
      - Dundee Community High School 1909-1992 (Box 50)
    - Durand
      - Durand Area High School 1905-1992 (Box 50)
  - E-G
    - East Detroit
      - East Detroit High School 1924-1991 (Box 50)
    - East Grand Rapids
      - East Grand Rapids High School 1925-1992 (Box 50)
    - East Jordan
      - East Jordan High School 1912-1992 (Box 51)
    - East Lansing
      - East Lansing High School 1918-1992 (Box 51)
      - Parker Collegiate School 1928-1931 (Box 51)
    - East Tawas
      - East Tawas High School 1915-1956 (Box 51)
        (also known as Tawas Area Rural Agricultural High School, see also Tawas City)
      - St. Joseph High School 1926-1940 (Box 51)
    - Eaton Rapids
      - Eaton Rapids High School 1903-1992 (Box 51)
    - Eau Claire
      - Eau Claire 1917-1992 (Box 51)
    - Eben Junction
      - Rock River Township Rural Agricultural School (Eben High School) 1926-1947 (Box 52)
    - Ecorse
      - Ecorse High School 1928-1992 (Box 52)
      - St. Francis Xavier High School 1940-1969 (Box 52)
    - Edenville
      - Edenville Township High School 1939 (Box 52)
    - Edmore
      - Edmore/Montabella High School 1923-1975 (Box 52)
    - Edwardsburg
      - Edwardsburg High School 1915-1992 (Box 52)
    - Elberta
      - Elberta 1929-1949 (Box 52)
    - Elk Rapids
      - Elk Rapids (Cherryland) High School 1905-1992 (Box 52)
    - Elkton
      - Elkton High School 1927-1959 (Box 52)
    - Ellsworth
      - Ellsworth High School 1933-1961 (Box 53)
    - Elsie
      - Ovid-Elsie High School 1911-1992 (Box 53)
    - Empire
      - Empire Rural Agricultural School 1938-1941 (Box 53)
    - Engadine (Garfield Township)
      - Engadine High School 1941-1959 (Box 53)
    - Erie
      - Mason (Senior/Consolidated) High School 1954-1992 (Box 53)
    - Escanaba
      - Escanaba (Area) High School 1902-1992 (Box 53)
      - Holy Name High School 1955-1970 (Box 53)
      - St. Joseph High School 1926-1953 (Box 53)
    - Essexville
      - Essexville Garber High School 1966-1992 (Box 53)
      - St. John High School 1930-1967 (Box 54)
    - Evart
      - Evart High School 1902-1992 (Box 54)
    - Ewen
      - Ewen (Trout Creek) High School 1920-1967 (Box 54)
    - Fairgrove
      - Fairview Rural Agricultural School/Akron-Fairgrove High School 1926-1972 (Box 54)
    - Fairview
      - Fairview High School 1936-1992 (Box 54)
    - Farmington
      - Clarenceville High School 1943-1952 (Box 54)
      - Farmington High School 1919-1992 (Box 54)
      - Harrison High School 1972-1992 (Box 55)
      - Hillel Day School of Metropolitan Detroit (see Detroit) (Box 55)
      - North Farmington High School 1964-1992 (Box 55)
      - Our Lady of Mercy High School 1965-1992 (Box 55)
      - Our Lady of Sorrows 1958-1970 (Box 55)
    - Farwell
      - Farwell (Area) (Rural Agricultural) High School 1928-1992 (Box 55)
    - Felch
      - Felch High School 1968 (Box 55)
    - Fennville
      - Fennville High School 1917-1991 (Box 55)
    - Fenton
      - Fenton High School 1905-1992 (Box 56)
      - Lake Fenton High School 1962-1992 (Box 56)
    - Ferndale
      - Ferndale High School 1959-1992 (Box 56)
      - Lincoln High School 1921-1958 (Box 56)
      - St. James High School 1929-1970 (Box 56)
    - Fife Lake
      - Forest Area High School (Fife Lake Township Unit High School) 1950-1992 (Box 56)
    - Flat Rock
      - Flat Rock High School 1928-1992 (Box 57)
      - Woodhaven High School 1975-1992 (Box 57)
    - Flint
      - Ainsworth/Carman-Ainsworth High School 1961-1992 (Box 57)
      - All Saints High School 1946-1953 (Box 57)
      - Atherton (Community) High School 1957-1975 (Box 57)
      - Beecher High School 1936-1992 (Box 57)
      - Bendle (Senior) High School 1930-1974 (Box 58)
      - Bentley (Senior)High School 1958-1974 (Box 58)
      - Carman High School 1954-1985 (Box 58)
        (see also Ainsworth/Carman-Ainsworth)
      - Central (Community) High School 1930-1992 (Box 58)
      - Dye Community High School (later Carman High School) 1941-1960 (Box 58)
      - Michael Hamady High School 1963-1992 (Box 58)
      - Holy Redeemer High School 1954-1970 (Box 58)
      - Holy Rosary High School 1972-1992 (Box 58)
      - (Herbert) Hoover High School (later Carman High School) 1931-1961 (Box 59)
      - Kearsley (Community/Agricultural) High School 1939-1942 (Box 59)
      - Mandeville High School (later Carman High School?) 1950-1960 (Box 59)
      - Northern Community High School 1928-1992 (Box 59)
      - Northwestern High School 1964-1992 (Box 59)
      - (Luke M.) Powers Catholic High School/Education Center 1970-1985 (Box 59)
      - Sacred Heart High School 1958-1968 (Box 60)
      - St. Agnes High School 1953-1970 (Box 60)
      - St. John Vianney High School 1955-1970 (Box 60)
      - St. Mary's High School 1932-1939 (Box 60)
      - St. Matthew High School 1927-1970 (Box 60)
      - St. Michael's High School 1921-1970 (Box 60)
      - Southwestern (Community) High School (Academy) 1961-1992 (Box 60)
      - Technical High School 1941-1959 (Box 60)
      - Utley High School 1941-1960 (Box 60)
      - The Valley School 1970-1982 (Box 60)
      - Westwood Heights High School 1963 (Box 60)
    - Flushing
      - Flushing High School 1929-1992 (Box 60)
    - Fostoria (Box 61)
      - Fostoria High School 1937-1939 (Box 61)
    - Fowler
      - Fowler High School 1929-1992 (Box 61)
    - Fowlerville
      - Fowlerville High School 1921-1992 (Box 61)
    - Frankenmuth
      - Frankenmuth High School 1950-1992 (Box 61)
    - Frankfort
      - Frankfort High School 1910-1992 (Box 61)
    - Fraser
      - Fraser High School 1931-1942 (Box 61)
    - Frederic
      - Frederic (Rural Agricultural) High School 1926-1951 (Box 62)
    - Freeland
      - Freeland High School 1926-1992 (Box 62)
    - Freeport
      - Freeport High School 1929-1944 (Box 62)
    - Free Soil
      - Free Soil High School 1930-1935 (Box 62)
    - Fremont
      - Fremont High School 1905-1992 (Box 62)
    - Frontier
      - Frontier High School 1929-1942 (Box 62)
    - Fruitport
      - Fruitport High School 1934-1992 (Box 62)
    - Gagetown
      - Gagetown High School 1920-1943 (Box 62)
    - Gaines
      - Gaines Consolidated (Agricultural) School 1929-1961 (Box 62)
    - Galesburg
      - Galesburg-Augusta High School 1916-1992 (Box 62)
    - Galien
      - Galien High School 1918-1992 (Box 63)
    - Garden City
      - Garden City High School 1951-1991 (Box 63)
      - Garden City West High School 1966-1982 (Box 63)
    - Gaylord
      - Gaylord (Public/Rural Agricultural) High School 1905-1992 (Box 63)
      - St. Mary (Cathedral) High School 1930-1992 (Box 63)
    - Genesee
      - Genesee High School 1982-1992 (Box 63)
    - Gibraltar
      - Oscar A. Carlson High School 1969-1992 (Box 64)
    - Gladstone
      - Gladstone High School 1905-1992 (Box 64)
    - Gladwin
      - Gladwin (Rural Agricultural) High School 1921-1992 (Box 64)
      - Winegars Public High School 1959 (Box 64)
    - Glen Arbor
      - The Leelanau Schools 1931-1992 (Box 64)
    - Gobles
      - Gobles High School 1915-1992 (Box 64)
    - Goodrich
      - Goodrich High School 1922-1992 (Box 65)
    - Grand Blanc
      - Grand Blanc High School 1922-1992 (Box 65)
    - Grand Haven
      - Akeley Hall for Girls 1915-1926 (Box 65)
      - Grand Haven Senior High School 1905-1992 (Box 65)
    - Grand Ledge
      - Grand Ledge High School 1929-1992 (Box 65)
      - Grand Ledge Academy 1958-1984 (Box 66)
    - Grand Marais
      - Grand Marais High School 1908-1946 (Box 66)
    - Grand Rapids
      - Catholic Central 1927-1992 (Box 66)
      - Central High School 1905-1992 (Box 66)
      - Creston High School 1927-1992 (Box 66)
      - (George A.) Davis Vocational and Technical High School 1926-1944 (Box 66)
      - East Christian High School (see Grand Rapids Christian High School) (Box 66)
      - East Grand Rapids High School (see East Grand Rapids) (Box 66)
      - Forest Hills Central (formerly Forest Hill High School) 1959-1992 (Box 66)
      - Forest Hill Northern High School 1974-1992 (Box 67)
      - Furniture Capital Air Service School 1930 (Box 67)
      - Grand Rapids Baptist Academy 1978-1992 (Box 67)
      - Grand Rapids Christian High School (consolidation of East Christian High School and Central Christian High School) 1922-1992 (Box 67)
      - Kelloggsville High School 1938-1980 (Box 67)
      - Kenowa Hills High School 1965-1992 (Box 67)
      - Marywood Academy 1906-1974 (Box 67)
        (includes sacred heart academy)
      - Mt. Mercy Academy 1924-1974 (Box 67)
      - Northview High School 1965-1992 (Box 67)
      - Ottawa Hills High School 1927-1991 (Box 68)
      - South Christian High School 1954-1992 (Box 68)
      - South High School 1910-1967 (Box 68)
      - Theological (Christian Reform) School 1905 (Box 68)
      - Union High School 1912-1992 (Box 68)
      - West Catholic High School 1965-1992 (Box 68)
      - Wyoming Park High School (see Wyoming) (Box 68)
    - Grandville
      - Grandville High School 1929-1992 (Box 69)
      - Calvin Christian High School 1969 (Box 69)
    - Grant
      - Grant High School 1929-1992 (Box 69)
    - Grass Lake
      - Grass Lake (Junior/Senior) High School 1909-1992 (Box 69)
    - Grayling
      - Grayling High School 1907-1992 (Box 69)
    - Greenland Township
      - Greenland Township High School (see Mass) (Box 69)
    - Greenville
      - Greenville High School 1906-1992 (Box 69)
    - Grosse Ile
      - Grosse Ile High School 1921-1992 (Box 70)
    - Grosse Pointe
      - Academy of the Sacred Heart 1930-1969 (Box 70)
      - Our Lady Star of the Sea 1963-1992 (Box 70)
      - South High School 1924-1992 (Box 70)
      - Country Day School 1909-1953 (Box 70)
      - St. Paul High School 1930-1970 (Box 70)
      - University School 1949-1969 (Box 70)
      - University/Leggett High School 1966-1992 (Box 71)
    - Grosse Pointe Woods
      - Grosse Pointe North High School 1970-1992 (Box 71)
    - Gwinn
      - Gwinn High School 1911-1992 (Box 71)
  - H-L
    - Hadley
      - Hadley High School 1940 (Box 71)
    - Hale
      - Hale High School (Plainfield Township Rural Agricultural High School) 1963-1992 (Box 71)
    - Hamilton
      - Hamilton (Junior/Senior Community) High School 1964-1992 (Box 71)
    - Hamtramck
      - Hamtramck High School 1918-1992 (Box 72)
      - Immaculate Conception Ukrainian Catholic High School 1962-1992 (Box 72)
      - St. Florian High School 1944-1992 (Box 72)
      - St. Ladislaus High School 1935-1982 (Box 72)
    - Hancock
      - Hancock Central High School 1905-1992 (Box 72)
      - St. Patrick High School 1931 (Box 72)
      - Suomi College Academy 1920-1930 (Box 72)
    - Hanover
      - Hanover High School 1927-1965 (Box 72)
    - Harbor Beach
      - Harbor Beach (Community) High School 1921-1992 (Box 73)
      - Our Lady of Lake Huron High School 1942-1970 (Box 73)
    - Harbor Springs
      - Harbor Springs High School 1921-1992 (Box 73)
    - Harper Woods
      - Bishop Gallagher High School 1965-1991 (Box 73)
      - Harper Woods High School 1952-1992 (Box 73)
      - Lutheran High School East 1958-1992 (Box 73)
      - Notre Dame 1958-1992 (Box 74)
      - Regina High School 1960-1992 (Box 74)
    - Harris
      - Bark River-Harris High School (Central High School) 1935-1992 (Box 74)
    - Harrison
      - Harrison Community High School (also known as Hayes Township Agricultural High School) 1929-1992 (Box 74)
    - Harrisville
      - Alcona Community High School (see Lincoln) (Box 74)
      - Harrisville Consolidated High School 1923-1958 (Box 74)
    - Hart
      - Hart High School 1921-1992 (Box 74)
    - Hartford
      - Hartford High School 1907-1992 (Box 75)
    - Hartland
      - Hartland (Senior/Consolidated) High School 1923-1992 (Box 75)
    - Haslett
      - Haslett (Rural Agricultural) High School 1906-1992 (Box 75)
    - Hastings
      - Hastings (Area) High School 1910-1992 (Box 75)
    - Hazel Park
      - Hazel Park High School 1923-1992 (Box 75)
    - Hemlock
      - Hemlock High School 1925-1987 (Box 76)
    - Henderson
      - Henderson High School 1935 (Box 76)
    - Hermansville
      - Hermansville High School 1925-1970 (joined with Powers-Spalding to become North Central High School in Powers) (Box 76)
    - Hersey
      - Hersey Township Agricultural School 1929-1953 (Box 76)
    - Hesperia
      - Hesperia (Community) High School 1921-1992 (Box 76)
    - Hickory Corners
      - W.K. Kellogg Consolidated Agricultural High School (became Gull Lake Community High School) 1942-1970 (Box 76)
        (see also Richland)
    - Highland